Mohd Adnan Khalid

Pharmacist

- adnankhalid2323@gmail.com
- +919044509741
- Jaunpur, Uttar Pradesh, India
- in www.linkedin.com/in/mohdadnankhalid

PROFILE

Dedicated pharmacist with a record of success reviewing patient data and providing superb customer service. Demonstrated exceptional time management and problem-solving skills in a high-volume, 24-hour pharmacy. Foster a positive, supportive care environment for patients and their families. Maintain compliance of clinical records with all company policies and legal requirements. Retain patients by providing reliable knowledge and care, timely follow-up, and improved adherence. fluent in English, Hindi and Urdu.

Pharmacist with 7+ years of experience in using strong interpersonal skills and extensive medication knowledge to help patients with their needs. Top achievements include earning 98% positive feedback in patient surveys during 2021 to 2022

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

 January 2017 –
 Ku

 March 2018
 Dis

Kumar Maternity & Surgical Nursing Home, Pharmacist Assistant

Dispense Prescriptions.

Jaunpur, India Receive prescriptions and communicate required medications to

pharmacist.

Prescriptions and communicate required medications to pharmacist. Implemented for innovative solutions to automate data management and remove paper tracking systems.

Designed and managed improved guidelines and processes, maximizing team productivity and reducing administrative errors to less than 0.1%. Monitor medication stock and communicate with pharmacist when supplies are low.

January 2016 – March 2018 Jaunpur, India Deep Children Hospital, Pharmacist Assistant

Dispense Prescriptions.

Receive prescriptions and communicate required medications to

pharmacist.

prescriptions and communicate required medications to pharmacist. Implemented for innovative solutions to automate data management

maximizing team productivity and reducing administrative errors to less

and remove paper tracking systems.

Designed and managed improved guidelines and processes,

than 0.1%.

Monitor medication stock and communicate with pharmacist when supplies are low.

October 2020 – January 2021 Bahraich, India District Hospital, Bahraich, Pharmacist Internship

Dispense Prescriptions.

Consulted with physicians and patients about medication dosage, drug interactions.

Disease management, and potential side effects of medication with 100% accuracy.

Shadowed pharmacist, filling and dispensing 75% of prescriptions, performing technician duties and technical processes.

Counseled 40+ patients, under the supervision of the pharmacist, with a caring and supportive attitude, following HIPAA regulations.

Consulted with physicians and patients about medication dosages and drug interactions, leading to an 82% customer retention rate.

February 2021 – November 2022 Jaunpur, India Teerthraj Hospital, Pharmacist Assistant

Dispense Prescriptions.

Receive prescriptions and communicate required medications to pharmacist.

prescriptions and communicate required medications to pharmacist. Implemented for innovative solutions to automate data management and remove paper tracking systems.

Designed and managed improved guidelines and processes, maximizing team productivity and reducing administrative errors to less than 0.1%. Monitor medication stock and communicate with pharmacist when supplies are low.

February 2021 – present Jaunpur, India **Kumar Maternity & Surgical Nursing Home,** Pharmacist Assistant Dispense Prescriptions.

Consulted with physicians and patients about medication dosage, drug interactions, disease management, and potential side effects of medication with 100% accuracy.

Shadowed pharmacist, filling and dispensing 75% of prescriptions, performing technician duties and technical processes.

Counseled 40+ patients, under the supervision of the pharmacist, with a caring and supportive attitude, following HIPAA regulations.

Consulted with physicians and patients about medication dosages and drug interactions, leading to an 82% customer retention rate.

EDUCATION

2018 – 2020 Lucknow, India Lucknow Institute of Pharmacy, Lucknow, Diploma In Pharmacy

2016 – 2018 jaunpur, India

V.B.S Purvanchal University Jaunpur, Master of Science

LANGUAGES

English Hindi Urdu

SKILLS

Exceptional patient care and interaction • Pharmaceutical distribution familiarity

Abbreviations comprehension • Inventory management

Extensive medical terminology knowledge • Storage awareness

Efficient, accurate And Team Player • Communicator • Innovator • Team Player • Thinker

Bill Maker • word processor operators • Prescription • Call Monitoring • Quality Assurance

Organization Skills • Medicare

INTERESTS

Listning Old Bollywood Song • Swimming

CERTIFICATES

Pharmacist

I am working from home since couple of weeks and my internet speed is more than 30MB per second for download and 5MB per second for upload